<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<changelogs>
	<changelog>
		<element>mod_ccctwoclick</element>
		<type>module</type>
		<version>3.0.1</version>
		<fix>
			<item>URL validation now uses parse_url() instead of filter_var() to support URLs with special characters (e.g., Google Maps embed URLs with exclamation marks in query parameters).</item>
		</fix>
	</changelog>
	<changelog>
		<element>mod_ccctwoclick</element>
		<type>module</type>
		<version>3.0.0</version>
		<addition>
			<item>Installer script to require Joomla 5.4+ and migrate legacy params (privacy link fields, allowfullscreen false value, overlay position).</item>
			<item>Privacy card and privacy bar UI with configurable placement, integrated or separate layout, and style controls (colors, radius, shadows).</item>
			<item>Consent controls: toggle/button/both, load delay, consent scope (module/domain/global), session or local storage, and YouTube/Vimeo autoplay.</item>
			<item>Responsive video container with ratio presets, background overlay color/blur controls, and region label override for accessibility.</item>
			<item>Link picker field to select privacy links from articles or menu items.</item>
			<item>Modular template partials (helpers, variables, card, bar, inline CSS) and dedicated JS asset for behavior.</item>
		</addition>
		<change>
			<item>Template markup restructured with BEM classes and data attributes; behavior moved from inline scripts to the JS asset.</item>
			<item>CSS rewritten to style placeholders, cards, bars, toggle control, and reduced-motion handling.</item>
			<item>iFrame source handling now accepts embed codes, normalizes protocol-relative/relative URLs, validates URLs, and uses a fallback title.</item>
			<item>Parameter UI reorganized into tabs (Before, Privacy, iFrame, Behaviour, Advanced) with updated help text and translations.</item>
			<item>Update server URL moved to GitHub releases; manifest metadata updated for version 3.0.0.</item>
			<item>Donation message and module description text updated.</item>
		</change>
		<remove>
			<item>Legacy privacy link params (displayprivacypolicy, privacypolicy, privacypolicytext) replaced by the new privacy link fields.</item>
			<item>Legacy button position settings for reveal/disable controls in favor of the privacy card layout.</item>
		</remove>
		<note>
			<item>Major update: requires Joomla 5.4+.</item>
			<item>Backup your site before upgrading.</item>
		</note>
	</changelog>
</changelogs>
